# </salt>

School of applied technology



# Fabrizio Onorio

My passion for learning, solving complex issues, and making products that people enjoy using, brought me to Salt. I have worked several years in the retail industry, worked in many teams, and covered different leadership positions.

 $\ensuremath{\text{I'm}}$  energetic and proactive, and  $\ensuremath{\text{I}}$  enjoy working and collaborating with others.

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

#### General

JavaScript Ruby on Rails

#### Backend

NodeJS ExpressJS REST GraphQL MongoDB/PostgreSQL

#### Frontend

TypeScript
React
Redux
Webpack
HTML
jQuery
CSS/SASS/styled-components

#### Tools and technologies

Visual Studio Code
Handlebars/Mustache
Mocha/Jest
Docker
Git+GitHub
GitHub Actions
AWS
Cloud Platforms (MongoDB Atlas,
ElephantSQL, Heroku, Netlify,
Contentful)
TDD
Agile work methods

#### Links

GitHub LinkedIn Portfolio

#### Languages

Italian: Native English: Fluent

Norwegian: Intermediate

# **EDUCATION & TRAINING**

# Full Stack JavaScript - School of Applied Technology </salt>

Intensive three month training program for full stack web development with a focus on TDD, mob programming, and applied learning.

#### Full Stack Ruby on Rails - Le Wagon

July 2021 - September 2021 Intensive 10 weeks training program with a focus on building full-stack applications with Rails.

# English - BSGS College

November 2014 - March 2015

## Economics - University of Brescia

2006 - 2007

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Store Manager - Zara - Oslo

May 2017 - June 2021

Managed a store with over 80 employees with focus on training, following best practices and leading the team to reach the company goals. Performed sales analysis on a daily basis for making decisions leading to reaching the sales targets of in-store sales and online sales.

#### Department Manager - H&M - London

March 2015 - March 2017

Responsible for the sales of the womenswear department, the layout, and coordination of the logistic team.

# Store Manager - Pull and Bear - Italy

July 2008 - October 2014

Responsible for the sales, training of the team, operations/logistics of the store and layout according to the company guidelines.